Take back the future!
Kaiji returns to the silver screen!
And we give you loyal anime watchers a sneak peek!
Mikoko, the leading (and only) lady of the Kaiji anime!
Ever since her introduction, she's been popular among those in the know online!
Instead of her, the leading lady of Kaiji 2 will be...
Yuriko Yoshitaka!
She plays the daughter of Ishida, who lost his life in the first movie!
They were all so frank that there were no misunderstandings at all.
The rest of the cast were fabulous.
And the fantastic setting is intriguing.
I really enjoyed the characters.
What's the secret of the new game!?
Kaiji 2: Jinsei Dakkai Game, this November 5th!
究極のモンスターマシンの本丸
Kaiji challenges the demonic trays, core of the Bog!
魔性の３段クルーンに挑むカイジ
いけー！
Go!
フロア全体を沼と逆方向に傾ける
奇想天外 空前絶後の奇策！
He tilts the floor itself in the opposite direction of the Bog!
An unprecedented, unique plan!
それに対し 一条は何と
But Ichijou tilts the Bog to match the floor's tilt!
沼をフロアと同じ方向に傾き返す
傾斜かぶせで抗う
必死の攻防！
カイジの残金は200万
500発を切る
Kaiji now has only two million left! Only 500 shots!
迫る破滅 壊滅の時！
Kaiji's doom closes in!
策と策 執念と執念の激突！
Their tricks, their determination clash!
A Sure Winner
Please... I don't need a lot of luck...
頼む　強運なんかじゃ
なくっていい！
I'm not looking for a miracle...
奇跡も要らない　平運！
起こってくれよ！
Just a little bit... I just need one thing to go my way...
ごく普通の現象！確率！
起きてくれ！
Just make things happen how they normally should!
Please, make it happen!
フフフ… ダメ ダーメ
Now, now, Kaiji.
台を叩くのは御法度だぜ
カイジくん
You should know that striking the machine is against the rules.
分かってるはずだろ？
フフフ… とんだ悪あがき
It's not going to do you any good.
うるせえ　黙ってろ
Shut the fuck up!
まだ勝負はついてねえ
We're not done yet!
Not yet!
ついてねえんだ
フフフ… どうしたどうした？
Oh, is something wrong?
え？カイジくん
クッ… ふざけるな
Give me a break! This isn't the end!
終わってたまるか！このまま…
It can't end like this!
終われるかよ！
I'll hit the jackpot!
出す！出すんだ！
Somehow, I'll hit it!
何としても 出す！クソッ！
Dammit! This makes no sense!
あるかよ こんなことって
ここまで いくつにも
積み上げた仕掛け
I've done so much to make sure this goes my way!
勝ちの仕組みを
念入りに積み上げた
I've planned out every last detail!
それが 結局は
不遇 流れ アンラッキー
But everything's going his way!
そんなもののために
消えるっていうのか？
Will that be my end!?
あった！
There it is!
見える！一筋の光明！
He sees it! A ray of hope!
This will be my victory! My sure path to the jackpot!
こんな所に勝利
勝ちへの確実な道があった！
ありやがった！
There it is!
勝てる！
I can win! This is how I can win!
このままなら 勝てる！
But! But!!!
だが しかし！
あー
クソッ
Aw shit.
切れた
ああ…
He's out...
お… 終わっちまった
カイジさん…
It's over.
Kaiji...
カイジくん…
カイジさん…
イヒ イヒ イヒ…
悪運尽きたな カイジくん
Looks like your luck's run out, Kaiji.
You're going back.
お帰りだ　ハハハ…
Someone give me a hand. He's probably too shocked to stand up.
手伝ってやれ　どうやら
ショックで足腰が立たないらしい
Back off.
よせよ
誰が言ったよ？終了なんてよ
Who said I was done yet?
Kaiji!
カイジくん
ん？
ハハハ… からっけつが！
The suitcase is empty! You're out of money, you're done!
終わりなんだよ 金がなくなりゃ！
That's how casinos work.
それがカジノの鉄則だ
お前はもう客じゃない
You're not a guest anymore! You're just broke trash!
ただの文無しのクズなんだよ
Trash! Trash trash trash!
クズ！クズ！クズ！クズ！
帰れ 地下へ！
Back in your hole!
あ？虫ケラめ オケラ 文無し！
You penniless worm!
金なら…
I've got some.
I've got some more money.
金なら ある！
あ？金はあるだと？
You have money?
トイレだ
I'm taking a leak.
I'm not done yet.
いいな まだ終わっちゃいねえ
Don't let anyone else touch it.
誰にも触らせるな
カ… カイジくん！
Kaiji?
おっちゃん 遠藤さんも
ちょっといいか？
Pops. Endoh.
Come with me.
あ？あ… ああ…
まさか…
Seriously?
金を貸せってんじゃあるまいな？
Don't tell me you want to borrow more money.
Why not?
あるまいなって それ以外何が…
What else would I even—
言っとくがもう金はない
I'm all out!
もうこれ以上 貸せる金なんざ
びた一文…
I don't have anything left to lend to you!
そっちの男が持ってるカバン
あ？
How about the money in that bag he's holding?
金だろ　額は1000万
It's money. Probably about ten million.
え？
この賭けに負けた時
You've got it so you can bail out the second I lose.
すぐ逃げられるように
用意した金が入ってるんだよな
全部 知ってんだよ
I know exactly what you're up to!
頼む　貸してくれ
Please! Lend me that money!
このままじゃ あんただって
破滅だ！遠藤さん
If I lose here, your goose is cooked too!
ふざけるな！疫病神が！
Fuck off!
You're jinxed!
冗談じゃねえ！突っ込めるか！
Are you just fucking with me!?
この金は 俺の最後の命綱！
This money is my last lifeline!
こいつで高飛びしなきゃ…
If I don't have it ready to ditch with...
待ってるのは…
You know what's waiting for me, right?
地獄
It's hell.
Hell on earth.
地獄じゃねえか
そんな命銭を
You think I'm going to give up that lifeline to a luckless loser like you?
おめえみてえなクズの能なし
You made it to the critical moment! All you needed was one shot!
この肝心要 勝負所で
ただの１発 １発だぞ？
１発だけだ！それすら
決めることのできないゴミ野郎に
That's all you needed, but you blew it! You think I have any more money to waste on you?
つぎ込めるか！
I was a fool.
バカだった
お前の口車に乗った俺が
I was a complete fool to listen to you.
バカだった… 情けねえ
あばよ
Goodbye.
Endoh!
遠藤さん…
幕は下りたんだよ
It's curtains for you.
Not yet!
まだだ
見つけたんだよ　勝つ道
I've found a path to victory.
確実な勝利を
A sure winner.
この上 何を企んでいやがる
What is he planning?
そ… それ 本当か？カイジくん
Really, Kaiji!?
今さらウソついてどうすんだよ
Would I lie?
これでもまだ逃げ出す気か？
遠藤さん
Are you really going to run away now?
Come back.
帰ってこい
帰ってこい！
Come back!
遠藤！
Endoh!
We can't back out of this fight now!
勝負だろ！ここでいかずに
どうするよ！
ボケたか？遠藤！
Are you nuts?
We're inches away! Inches away from 700 million!
勝てるんだよ あと数センチ
数センチで７億に届く！
くるとは…
There's no guarantee it'll pay out.
限らねえだろ
えっ？
Even if you're telling the truth, there's no guarantee.
今の話が本当だとしても
くるとは限らねえ
何言ってんだよ
今やろうとしてることは
What!?
It's as sure as spinning the lottery until there's only one ball left!
言ってみれば福引きのガラガラを
最後の玉まで回そうって
言ってるようなもんだ
It's guaranteed to win!
必ずだ！絶対 当たる！
It may be guaranteed, but there's no guarantee it'll happen in ten million!
その｢必ず｣が 俺のこの1000万で
くるとは限らねえだろ！
Right, Kaiji!?
ええ？そうだろうが カイジ！
外れ 失敗する可能性も
あるだろうが！
It can still fail!
抜かすな！
うっ
Don't give me that!
屁みたいなこと
言ってんじゃねえ！
Don't pussy out like that!
It could fail? So what!
外れる？失敗？
それがどうした！
If it wails, we may be sunk...
沈めばいいだろ そん時は！
そん時は 地の底暮らしもアリだ！
But we can keep living, sunk in the earth!
You need to be willing to put that on the line!
覚悟しろよ そのぐらい！
Plus...
第一 今を逃げられたとして
Even if you run away, what happens then?
その後は？
借金取りを恐れて 外国でひたすら
息を潜めて過ごすってか？
Are you just gonna hide from the loan sharks in some foreign country?
Is that all you want out of life!?
いいのかよ それで？
What's in it for you?
何がある？そうやって逃げた先に
All you'll be able to do is drink your money away while you wait to die!
酒びたりで
虎の子の金を食い潰して
そんな半ボケの人生が関の山
そんな未来があんたの望みかよ？
Is that the future you want?
違うだろ？あんたの望む未来は
そんなんじゃないだろ！
It isn't, right? You don't want that!
分かれよ 遠藤さん！
Come on, Endoh! Listen to me here!
分かってくれよ！
Follow that ray!
迷ったら 望みだろ
That ray of hope!
希望だろ！
Life is only really worth living when you have hope!
希望に進むのが
気持ちのいい人生ってもんだろ
Even if we sink into that hell!
仮に
地の底に 沈もうともだ
遠藤さん 聞いてくれ
Listen to this, Endoh.
約束しよう
もし地に沈むことになったら
I promise you.
If we end up trapped in that hell...
Every month, on payday, I'll buy you two beers.
毎月 給料日に
ビールを２本 振る舞おう
遠藤さんが くたばるまで
Every month until you die.
Make it three.
３本だ
Three beers.
缶ビール３本
Three and it's a deal.
約束したぞ
ああ 分かった！
Got it!
Wait!
待て！
え？
／人◕ ‿‿ ◕人＼
The contract.
借用書
ええっ？
Now, of all times!?
こんな時に？
Problem?
こんな時もクソもあるか！
Jeez...
…ったく
ほら これでいいだろ？
Here, are you happy now?
Sorry I don't have a chop with me.
ハンコは持ってたよな？
Anyway, I'm going back.
じゃあ行くぜ
あんまり間を空けて
I don't want them to decide I'm not coming back and let someone else play.
棄権にされちゃ たまらねえからな
なんだ あのガキは？
What's with that kid?
追いつめられてるくせに
逆に生き生きしてやがる
Now that he's well and truly fucked, he brightens up!
頼りになるんだか ならねえんだか
I don't even know if that makes him reliable or a flake!
Endoh...
遠藤はん
言っても始まらねえ
ここまで来たら
There's no point in even talking about it.
All we can do now is rely on him.
もう託すしかねえ
あの男に
Sorry to keep you waiting, Ichijou.
待たせたな 一条
This time I'll finish the Bog off.
今度こそ そいつの
息の根を止めるぜ
With this.
こいつで
すでに5000万を溶かし
Having burned through 50 million,
さらに1000万 合計6000万！
Kaiji adds another 10 million! His total bet is 60 million!
見物人の誰しもが抱く
狂気の沙汰！
No one in the audience expected this crazy move!
Where did you get that money, you son of a bitch!?
貴様… その金 どうやって？
おっちゃんは？
気分が悪いんで少し休むとよ
Where's pops?
He's not feeling that hot, so he's taking a break.
Can't expect his nerves to hold through this.
悪くもなるさ
普通の神経ならな
Now you, doing this with a grin on your face... You I don't get.
この修羅場で生き生きしてる
お前の神経のほうが
どうかしてんだよ
別に生き生きなんかしてねえよ
I'm not exactly enjoying myself here.
その金 あんたが？
You lent him that money!?
I just couldn't say no.
まっ 貸さざるを得なくなってな
バカなことを！無駄金だ！
Are you insane? You're throwing it away!
かもしれねえ… が
Maybe.
But if I give up now, I won't be able to see it.
ここで下がっても見えねえのよ
That ray of hope.
希望ってやつがさ
That's it, though.
まあ その金がラスト
これで正真正銘 すっからかん
My honest-to-goodness bottom dollar.
しのぎゃ 今度こそ勝ちだよ
あんたの
Survive it, and you win.
何だよ そのあからさまな
迷惑顔は？
What are you making that face for?
I'm a valued guest as long as I have money.
それでも客商売か？
金を持ってきた以上 俺たちは客
That's how casinos work, right?
カジノの鉄則だろ　歓迎しろよ
Now get me another ten million Paqy.
交換だ　パッキー1000万
え？ああ…
Wait!
待て！
この金 調べさせてもらう
We need to check that money first!
何だと？何を今さら
What!?
What are you trying to say here!?
Shut up! Check him for magnets, too, he's been gone too long!
黙れ！それと磁気チェックだ
しばらくフロアを出たんだ
嫌なら台に座ることは許さない！
You're getting checked before you touch that machine again!
Kaiji undergoes another magnet check on Ichijou's orders!
有無を言わせぬ一条の言葉
カイジ 再び磁気チェックを受ける
Ichijou himself spends ten minutes checking the money!
さらに一条 自ら札束をチェック
10分が経過
How is this happening!?
何てこった
I thought it was over! Now there's more!?
終わったと思ったら予想外の延長
I survived the last round, but there's no guarantee I'll be so lucky this time.
さっきは何とかしのいだが
この1000万も
しのげるとは限らない
クッ… 時間を稼がないと
I need to buy time until my ultimate weapon—my trump card—arrives!
あれが…
最終兵器 切り札が届くまで
Hey.
おい
もういいだろ
いつまで待たせるつもりだ
How long are you gonna keep me waiting?
お前みたいなチンピラが
急に用意した金だ
I can never be too careful about money a thug like you comes up with out of nowhere.
怪しいに決まってる！
慎重になるのも当たり前だ
おいおい 元は俺の金だぜ
Hey, that's my money you're talking about!
What are you planning?
何を企んでる？
You're stalling. Why?
長引かせて 何か企んでるのか？
バッ バカ言え！もう少し待て！
Of course not! Just hold on a little longer!
店長
何だ？
Boss...
What?
実は さっきまで沼の横で見ていて
I've been watching from the side of the Bog, and I think I noticed something...
１つ 気になったことが
Really?
確かか？
偶然とも思えません
I don't think it's just a coincidence.
Now that I think of it...
そういえば…
I knew it! Lady Luck is on my side!
やはり 運は俺にある！
The heavens smile upon me!
天が味方した　勝てる！
I don't even need the remote to finish him off!
最終リモコンを待たず
押し切れる！
Very well. Let's play.
分かった
受ければいいんだろう？
交換してやれ
はっ
Give him his Paqy.
Yes, sir.
あの野郎 急に態度が
変わりやがった
Something changed his mind quick.
嫌な予感がしねえか？
I have a bad feeling about this.
へへへ　構わねえさ そんなこと
I don't give a shit.
ともかく さっさと
座っちまうこった
I'm just going to sit right down.
Right at the machine.
こいつの前に
よう 帰ってきたぜ　悪魔め
Yo. I'm back, you devil.
おいおい 戻ってきた
カイジだ！
Hey! He's back!
Kaiji!
カイジさん！
カイジさん
カイジくん
カイジ！
Kaiji!
虫ケラが！へへへ…
That maggot!
カイジ カイジ カイジ…
Kaiji! Kaiji!
どうぞ
ああ
Here you are.
All right, let's roll.
さて いくか
カイジ カイジ カイジ…
ラスト1000万
My last ten million...
カイジ 一条　それぞれの
勝利への確信が交差する
Kaiji and Ichijou's belief they will win intermingles in a final battle beyond all limits!
限界を超えた 最終決戦！
オラー！
They crash together!
突入！突入！突入！
They crash! They crash!!!
Proverbs of Kaiji Returns!
Listen to me here!
Follow that ray! That ray of hope!
Life is only really worth living when you have hope!
Even if we sink into that hell!